Charles M. Kurtz
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1843-1940, undated, Series 2:
  - Correspondence, January 1-5, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 577-623)
    (Herbert A. Levy, Wm. Semple, Kurtz family, D.B. Kurtz, R.C. McLean-editor of The Inland Architect, Julia S. Kurtz, Chas. P. Tower, A.L. Wyant, Holmes Smith, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, January 16-20, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 624-656)
  - Correspondence, January 21-25, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 657-686)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, R. Swain Gifford, Thos. W. Wood, Marcus Benjamin)
  - Correspondence, January 26-31, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 687-723)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, George McKinstry, R. Mc. Shustleff, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, February 1-5, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 724-756)
    (J.R. Murphy-Fine Arts Dept., World's Julia S. Kurtz, Geo. McKinstry, E.W. Perry, Thomas W. Wood, R. Swain Gifford, Tock-C.C. Starkweather)
  - Correspondence, February 6-15, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 757-791)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, J.R. Murphy-Dept. of Fine Arts, World's Fair, Laura Sedgwick Collins)
  - Correspondence, February 16-20, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 792-814)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, J.R.Murphy-Dept. of Fine Arts, World's Fair, F.E. Bartlett, James W. Ellsworth, Laura Daintry, H.C. Ives)
  - Correspondence, February 21-25, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 815-852)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Marcus Benjamin, D.B. Kurtz, J. Douglas Moultray, Tock-C.C. Starkweather, Wm. Semple)
  - Correspondence, February 26-29, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 853-876)
    (E. Frischhof for Chas. Sedelmeyer, Julia S. Kurtz, Mrs. A.L. Campbell, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, March 1-10, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 877-917)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, R. Swain Gifford, C. de Vivo, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, March 11-20, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 918-945)
    (Kurtz family, Sam. P. Avery, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Emery H. Barton, D. B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, March 21-25, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 946-977)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family, J.R. Murphy-Dept. of Art, World's Fair, F.D. Millet, Philo A. Otis)
  - Correspondence, March 26-31, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 978-1010)
    (Clara T.McChesney, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, M. Louise McLaughlin, C. Durand Chapman, H.C. Ives)
  - Correspondence, April 1-10, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 1011-1057)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, H. C. Ives, D.B. Kurtz, George H. Galt)
  - Correspondence, April 11-20, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 1058-1104)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, H. C. Ives, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, April 21-30, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 1105-1142)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, C.S. Harrington-National Academy of Design, Walter Gay, Marcus Benjamin)
  - Correspondence, May 1-10, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 1143-1179)
    (J.W. Beck-Fine Arts Committee, Charles M. Kurtz, M. Durand-Ruel, D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, H.F. Farney)
  - Correspondence, May 11-15, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 1180-1209)
    (H.C. Ives, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Marcus Benjamin)
  - Correspondence, May 16-20, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 1210-1234)
    (W. Lewis Fraser, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Chas. T. Yerkes, J.P. Davis, C.C. Starkweather, Stanford W. White)
  - Correspondence, May 21-30, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 1235-1278)
    (Jas. R. Ortgies, C. de Vivo, C. Harry Eaton, J.C. Nicole of Durand-Ruel, Louis C. Tiffany, Mrs. C.A. Plimpton, D.B. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Brayton Ives, J. Alden Weir, Chas. Edw. Brentwood-sp.? Chicago Society of Artists, Charles H. Springer)
  - Correspondence, June 1-15, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 1279-1310)
    (Jas. R. Ortgies, Geo. R. Davis, Irving R. Wiles, Kurtz family, George F. Foster-Sec. Frederick A. Stokes Co., Tock-C.C. Starkweather, E.A. Engler-Washington University, Marcus Benjamin, R.J. Menefee, Starkweather family, Stephenson family, John Tracey)
  - Correspondence, June 16-30, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 1311-1331)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, H.C. Ives, Kurtz family, Marcus Benjamin, Charles A. Platt, Clarence E. Young-World's Congress Auxiliary of Columbian Exposition, Stephenson family, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, July 1-10, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 1332-1353)
    (B.B. Vallentine-Evening Telegram, J. Douglas Moultray, D.F. Hasbrouck, Starkweather family, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, July 11-15, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 1354-1380)
    (D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Patty Thum, Charles M. Kurtz, Clarence E. Young, Kurtz family)
  - Correspondence, July 16-20, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 1381-1399)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family, D.B. Kurtz, Starkweather family)
  - Correspondence, July 21-25, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 1400-1427)
    (D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Dr. John Dickey, Starkweather family)
  - Correspondence, July 26-31, 1892 (Reel 4811, Frame 1428-1463)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family, D.B. Kurtz, Sam. Coleman)
  - Correspondence, August 1-5, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 1-28)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Marcus Benjamin, H.W. Mesdag, Charles Geron (translation by Kurtz on frame 33))
  - Correspondence, August 6-15, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 29-47)
    (D.B. Kurtz, H.C. Ives, T.P. McElrath for New York Press Club, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, August 16-25, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 48-81)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, C.C. Starkweather, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, August 26-31, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 82-109)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, L.J. Wall-Pres. Aug.Gast Litho.Co., Horace Seely, Halsey C. Ives, Geo. H. Story-Metropolitan Museum of Art)
  - Correspondence, September 1-10, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 110-143)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, C.C. Starkweather, Halsey C. Ives)
  - Correspondence, September 11-15, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 144-176)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, D.F. Hasbrouck, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, September 16-20, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 177-201)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Halsey C. Ives)
  - Correspondence, September 21-30, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 202-230)
    (Halsey C. Ives, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, T.L. Flood The Chautauquan)
  - Correspondence, October 2-10, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 231-267)
  - Correspondence, October 11-20, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 268-290)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Emily J. Lakey, Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz
  - Correspondence, October 21-31, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 291-321)
    (Henry Baldwin for Montague Marks editor of the The Art Amateur, Halsey C. Ives, Stephenson family, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family)
  - Correspondence, November 1-5, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 322-359)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Henry Blackborn?, Halsey C. Ives, R.F. Knoedler, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, November 6-10, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 360-393)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Halsey C. Ives, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, November 11-20, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 394-419)
    (Halsey C. Ives, H.W. Mesdag, Morton M. Casseday, Kentucky Agent for National Life Insurance Company of Vermont, John J. Enneking, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, November 21-30, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 420-457)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, R.C. McLean -editor of Inland Architect)
  - Correspondence, December 1-10, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 458-507)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Halsey C. Ives, Kurtz family, Starkweather family, Charles M. Kurtz, John J. Enneking, G.P. Engelhard-Pres., The Graphic)
  - Correspondence, December 11-15, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 508-549)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Edward Gay, Julia S. Kurtz, Marcus Benjamin, James Grant for John Wanamaker, Montague Marks-The Art Amateur)
  - Correspondence, December 16-20, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 550-581)
    (C.C. Ripley-Pres. of Kansas City Art Assoc., Charles M. Kurtz, A.L. Wyant, Hubert Vos, Julia S. Kurtz, Frances R. King-Hall for Seabrooke Comic Opera Company, Halsey C. Ives, D.F. Hasbrouck, Montague Marks)
  - Correspondence, December 21-25, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 582-606)
    (Clara McChesney, Halsey C. Ives, Sam. P. Avery, Julia S. Kurtz, Geo. McKinstry, D.W. Tryon, Kurtz family, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, December 26-31, 1892 (Reel 4812, Frame 607-673)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, H. Boltan Jones, John J. Enneking, David L. Haight for The University Club to Prof. J.F. Weir, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, John Singer Sargent, D. W. Tryon, Halsey C. Ives, J.F. Weir, Clara McChesney, Frederic P. Vinton-Sec., Boston Committee, J.F. Weir)
  - Miscellaneous Letters, 1893? (Reel 4812, Frame 674-691)
    (F.E. Bartlett, Halsey C. Ives, Charles M. Kurtz, Kurtz family, Starkweather family)
  - Correspondence, January 1-5, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 692-748)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Sarah Hallowell, Wm. Morgan, Wm. McKinstry, Hubert Vos, Halsey C. Ives, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles Ward Rhodes, Charles Barnard, D.F. Hasbrouck, J.D. Pierce for Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts)
  - Correspondence, January 6-10, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 749-776)
    (J. G. Brown, Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Wm. B. Tuthill, F.D. Millet, Halsey C. Ives)
  - Correspondence, January 11-15, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 777-799)
    (D. F. Hasbrouck, Geo. Inness, Halsey C. Ives, Charles M. Kurtz, Reichard & Co, Sara Hallowell, Wm. T. Evans)
  - Correspondence, January 16-20, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 800-853)
    (D.F. Hasbrouck, Halsey C. Ives, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Geo. Maynard, Sara Hallowell, Elliott F. Shepard, Starkweather family, W. Walton, Frederic P. Vinton)
  - Correspondence, January 21-25, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 854-876)
    (F. L. Hiffinson, Halsey C. Ives, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, George Barrie)
  - Correspondence, January 26-28, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 877-898)
    (H. Bolton Jones, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, John F. Weir)
  - Correspondence, January 29-31, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 899-923)
    (Halsey C. Ives, Julia S. Kurtz, H. Siddons Mowbray, Hawthorne Hill-The Engineering Magazine, Wm. Tuthill)
  - Correspondence, February 1-5, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 924-961)
    (D.B. Kurtz, Clara McChesney, Halsey C. Ives, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Wm. B. Tuthill, Wm. Kurtz-photographer, Mrs. Charles Barnard, D. W. Tryon)
  - Correspondence, February 6-10, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 962-991)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Wm. B. Tuthill, Halsey C. Ives, H. Bolton Jones?, Wm. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, February 11-15, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 992-1023)
    (C. Harry Eaton, H. Bolton Jones?, Charles M. Kurtz, Halsey C. Ives, Julia S. Kurtz, John J. Enneking)
  - Correspondence, February 16-20, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1024-1055)
    (R. Bartholemy, Halsey C. Ives, H. Thompson, Julia S. Kurtz, J. H. Twachtman, Starkweather family, Charles M. Kurtz, Walter Shirlaw, Stephenson family)
  - Correspondence, February 21-28, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1056-1084)
    (R. Swain Gifford, Charles M. Kurtz, Starkweather family, D. W. Tryon, Vinnie Ream Hoxie, John J. Enneking, Charles M. Kurtz, Geo. Barrie, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, March 1-5, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1085-1116)
    (Christine S. Breelin?, Julia S. Kurtz, Starkweather family, James. W. Ellsworth, Edward Moran, H. Bolton Jones, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, March 6-10, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1117-1132)
    (J. Alden Weir, Walter McEwan, H.W. Mesdag, Julia S. Kurtz, J.M. Bowles-editor of Modern Art, Daniel C. French, James Ellsworth)
  - Correspondence, March 11-15, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1133-1149)
    (D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, James William Pattison, Ellis Wainwright)
  - Correspondence, March 15-20, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1150-1171)
    (J.S. Dickerson-editor of The Graphic, Starkweather family, Thos. Hovenden, Julia S. Kurtz, E. H. Wuertz, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, March 21-31, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1172-1202)
    (J. S. Dickinson, Thomas Hovenden, Julia S. Kurtz, Ellis Wainwright, Charles M. Kurtz, Starkweather family, H. Bolton Jones)
  - Correspondence, April 1-10, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1203-1236)
    (Starkweather family, D.B. Kurtz, Thos. Hovenden, Wm. Semple, Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Kurtz family)
  - Correspondence, April 11-20, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1237-1271)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Starkweather family, J. M. Bowles, Robert C. Ogden, Kurtz family, Douglas Volk, E. Frischhof, Durand-Ruel, Wm. McKinstry)
  - Correspondence, April 21-30, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1272-1303)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, J. C. DeLeon, R.J. Mcmenefee)
  - Correspondence, May 1-10, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1304-1335)
    (J. M. Bowles, Rhoda Holmes Nicholls, Mary M. Bartlett, D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, D. W. Tryon, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, May 11-20, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1336-1368)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Starkweather family, Robert C. Ogden, Kurtz family, Henry Blackburn, Howard Seeley)
  - Correspondence, May 21-31, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1369-1387)
    (J. S. Dickerson, D.B. Kurtz, Sam. P. Avery, Ellis Wainwright)
  - Correspondence, June 1-10, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1388-1422)
    (Eastman Johnson, Ellis Wainwright, Walter MacEwen, Charles M. Kurtz, Marcus Benjamin, Stephenson family, Julia S. Kurtz, Geo. McKinstry)
  - Correspondence, June 11-20, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1423-1458)
    (Geo. H. Bogert, Eastman Johnson, F. E. Bartlett, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Starkweather family, Stephenson family, Geo. H. Bogert, Charles Ward Rhodes)
  - Correspondence, June 21-30, 1893 (Reel 4812, Frame 1459-1484)
    (Wm. H.? Howe, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Geo. McKinstry)
  - Correspondence, July 1-10, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 1-42)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, W.H. Howe, Julia S. Kurtz, Carlton WIggins, Wm. Tuthill, Walter L. Dean, D. F. Hasbrouck, Eastman Johnson, Thos. Hovenden)
  - Correspondence, July 11-15, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 43-64)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, T. W. Dewing, Julia S. Kurtz, W.H. Howe, Harrison S. Morris, Kurtz family)
  - Correspondence, July 16-20, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 65-82)
    (Starkweather family, Kurtz family, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Ellis Wainwright, W. H. Howe)
  - Correspondence, July 21-25, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 83-96)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Fred. Wood, D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, July 26-31, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 97-114)
    (R. Swain Gifford, Ch. Sedelmeyer, Eastman Johnson)
  - Correspondence, August 1-10, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 115-140)
    (D.B. Kurtz, W.H. Howe, Chas. Nagel, Ellis Wainwright, Charles M. Kurtz, Charles Ward Rhodes?, Robert C. Ogden, Stephenson family)
  - Correspondence, August 11-20, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 141-182)
    (Stephenson family, N. Grindicelli, Commissioner of Fine Arts for France, Columbian Exposition, Chas. Nagel, Charles Ward Rhodes, D. F. Hasbrouck, Irving R. Wiles, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, August 21-25, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 183-211)
    (Mary G. Bartlett, J. Francis Murphy, Charles Ward Rhodes, Stephenson family, A. B. Farquhar-Ex. Commissioner of World's Fair Board, John J. Boyle, Starkweather)
  - Correspondence, August 26-30, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 212-225)
    (Charles Sedelmeyer, W. E. Safford, Emery H. Barton, Charles Ward Rhodes)
  - Correspondence, September 1-10, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 226-256)
    (Stephenson family, Clara T. McChesney, D.B. Kurtz, Charles Ward Rhodes)
  - Correspondence, September 11-30, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 257-283)
    (Charles Ward Rhodes, Charles Sedelmeyer, Douglas Volk, Starkweather family, Stephenson family, Howard Seeley)
  - Correspondence, October 1-5, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 284-308)
    (D.B. Kurtz, letter fragment, Oct., 1893? probably after Jan. 1?, Morton M. Casseday, Eastman Johnson, E.G. Kennedy-H. Wunderlich & Co., Stephenson family, Charles Ward Rhodes, Marcus Benjamin)
  - Correspondence, October 6-10, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 309-333)
    (W.B. Conkey-publisher for 1893 Chicago Fair, Chas. G. Loring, Stephenson family, J. M Bowles, Charles Ward Rhodes, D.B. Kurtz, The Art Club of Philadelphia)
  - Correspondence, October 11-20, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 334-363)
    (Emery H. Barton, Morton M. Casseday, W. Schuyler, Starkweather family, Stephenson family, Charles Ward Rhodes, Holmes Smith-St. Louis School and Museum of Fine Arts, Douglas Volk)
  - Correspondence, October 21-31, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 364-393)
    (Marcus Benjamin, Charles Ward Rhodes, Stephenson family, Douglas Volk, Chas. G. Loring, Montague Marks, Mary G. Bartlett, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, November 1-10, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 394-419)
    (Charles Ward Rhodes, Stephenson family, Mary G. Bartlett, Julia S. Kurtz, Holmes Smith, Edwin H. Blashfield)
  - Correspondence, November 11-20, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 420-448)
    (Robert C. Ogden, H. von Baerley, John McEwen, Frank Gaiennie, Ellis Wainwright, W.M.R. French-Art Institute of Chicago, Chas. G. Loring, Walter Satterlee, Stephenson family, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, November 21-30, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 449-462)
    (Chas. G. Loring, Stephenson family, D.F. Hasbrouck, Chas. G. Lroing, I.M. Gaugengigl)
  - Correspondence, December 1-10, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 463-481)
    (N. Yamataka-Imperial Japanese Commissioner for the World's Columbian Exposition, Stephenson family, Mary G. Bartlett, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, December 11-20, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 482-498)
    (Geo. Barrie, Irving R. Wiles, L.A. Coonley, Stephenson family)
  - Correspondence, December 21-31, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 499-531)
    (William T. Evans, Charles M. Kurtz, Stephenson family, P.A. Gross, Geo. H. Story, N. Yamataka, Benoni Irwin, John D. Pierce, W.M.R. French, D.B. Kurtz, and Charles M. Kurtz letter partially undated, 30 December, probably should be 1892)
  - Letters, some incomplete, 1894? (Reel 4813, Frame 532-550)
    (Halsey C. Ives, Charles M. Kurtz, Stephenson family)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1-15, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 551-578)
    (J. Spencer Dickenson, Frank Gaiennie, Stephenson family, Geo. Barrie, Ellis Wainwright, D.B. Kurtz, Charles Ward Rhodes)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 16-31, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 579-619)
    (Wm. Semple, G. P. Engelhard, W. M. R. French, Stephenson family, Charles M. Kurtz, Charles Ward Rhodes, Clara T. McChesney, M. Knoedler & Co., Patty Thum)
  - Correspondence, February 1-10, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 620-640)
    (D.B. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, The Southern Magazine, Stephenson family, Morton M. Casseday, Wm. Semple)
  - Correspondence, February 11-20, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 641-665)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Halsey C. Ives, Stephenson family, Charles Ward Rhodes, J. Harrison Mills, Wm. Semple)
  - Correspondence, February 21-28, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 666-698)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Clara T. McChesney, John D. Pierce, Stephenson family, A. Guinchard & F. Fourniret-Export firm)
  - Correspondence, March 1-5, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 699-733)
    (St. Louis Exposition, Julia S. Kurtz, Wm. H. Howe, Charles M. Kurtz, Charles Ward Rhodes, T. Vernette Morse-The Arts magazine, J. C. Nicoll, D.W. Tryon)
  - Correspondence, March 6-7, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 734-766)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Geo. H. Holt, Halsey C. Ives, Charles Ward Rhodes, D.B. Kurtz, E.M. Scott, Stephenson family, Patty Thum)
  - Correspondence, March 8-10, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 767-797)
    (Frederick Dielman, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, William Merrit Chase, R. Swain Gifford, Eastman Johnson, Geo. W. Maynard, Charles Ward Rhodes)
  - Correspondence, March 11-20, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 798-822)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Holmes Smith, Harrison A. Morris-Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, Charles M. Kurtz, A. Guinchard & F. Fourniret)
  - Correspondence, March 21-31, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 823-841)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, John D. Pierce for Harrison S. Morris)
  - Correspondence, April 1-10, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 842-876)
    (Kurtz family, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, April 11-20, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 877-913)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Halsey C. Ives, Kurtz family, Stephenson family, firm of A. Guinchard & F. Fourniret)
  - Correspondence, April 21-30, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 914-944)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, F. Hopkinson Smith, Kurtz family, Charles Ward Rhodes, P.A. Gross, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, May 1-10, 1893 (Reel 4813, Frame 945-992)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, St. Louis Exposition, Stephenson family, Stephenson family)
  - Correspondence, May 11-20, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 993-1028)
    (Kurtz family, Stephenson family, A.B. Stanton, Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Metropolitan Museum of Art, Charles Ward Rhodes?, Marcus Benjamin)
  - Correspondence, May 21-25, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1029-1048)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Stephenson family, Julia S. Kurtz, Morton M. Casseday)
  - Correspondence, May 26-31, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1049-1077)
    (Halsey C. Ives, Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, A. Bartholemy, Walter McEwen, Stephenson family)
  - Correspondence, June 1-5, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1078-1108)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, A. Bartholemy)
  - Correspondence, June 6-10, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1109-1137)
    (Stephenson family, Julia S. Kurtz, Sara Hallowell, M. Knoedler & Co., Wm. Semple, Charles M. Kurtz, Robt. J. Wickenden, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, June 11-20, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1138-1174)
    (Walter McEwen, Charles Ward Rhodes, C.P. Tower-editor of The Paper Mill, Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Walter Smythe for Sir Arthur Sullivan, Emil K. Kegel)
  - Correspondence, June 21-30, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1175-1203)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Kurtz family, D.B. Kurtz, P.A. Gross, A. Guin chard & F. Fourniret)
  - Correspondence, July 1-5, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1204-1232)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, D.B. Kurtz, Halsey C. Ives, Morton Casseday, Julia S. Kurtz, Carl Marr, Ellis Wainwright, Hamilton Hamilton)
  - Correspondence, July 6-20, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1233-1257)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, F. Hopkinson Smith, Kurtz family, Charles Ward Rhodes, Mary MacMonnies)
  - Correspondence, July 21-31, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1258-1273)
    (Charles M. Kurtz, Julia S. Kurtz, Patty Thum, Chas. Sedelmeyer, Marcus Benjamin, Stephenson family, D.B. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, August 1-5, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1274-1290)
    (Wm. H. Howe, Kurtz family, Charles Ward Rhodes, D.B. Kurtz, V. Raffaëlli, Halsey C. Ives)
  - Correspondence, August 6-10, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1291-1328)
    (Arthur Parton, John P. Davis, Charles Ward Rhodes, D.F. Hasbrouck, D. B. Kurtz, Clara McChesney, Starkweather family, Frederick Dielman, E.G. Kennedy, Robert C. Ogden, Morton M. Casseday, Halsey C. Ives, Charles M. Kurtz)
  - Correspondence, August 11-15, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1329-1367)
    (Benoni Irwin, Charles M. Kurtz, W. Scott Thurber, Irving R. Wiles, D.W. Tryon, Halsey C. Ives, Charles Ward Rhodes, W. Scott Thurber, Geo. F. Brownell, Durand-Ruel, Charles L. Freer, Howard Mansfield, Boussod Valadon & Co., Ellis Wainwright, Starkweather family, A. Bartholemy, W.T. Bishop)
  - Correspondence, August 16-20, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1368-1381)
    (Charles Ward Rhodes, Ellis Wainwright, Patty Thum, Frederick Dielman)
  - Correspondence, August 21-31, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1382-1398)
    (? Bill, H.W. Mills, Julia S. Kurtz, R. Swain Gifford, Emma Schuchman?, A. Bartholemy)
  - Correspondence, September 1-10, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1399-1418)
    (Julia S. Kurtz, Charles M. Kurtz, Geo. H. Story, William Schaus, Oscar Mattiegen, Commissioner of Fine Arts for Denmark)
  - Correspondence, September 11-15, 1894 (Reel 4813, Frame 1419-1436)